- id: k-jinmeiyo-4e58
  prompt: "Meanings: power, multiplication, record\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: の.る, の.せる"
  answers:
    - 乘
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-4e9e
  prompt: "Meanings: rank, follow\nOnyomi: ア\nKunyomi: つ.ぐ"
  answers:
    - 亞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-4f86
  prompt: "Meanings: come, due, next\nOnyomi: ライ, タイ\nKunyomi: く.る, きた.る, きた.す, き.たす"
  answers:
    - 來
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-4f5b
  prompt: "Meanings: France\nOnyomi: ブツ, フツ\nKunyomi: ほとけ"
  answers:
    - 佛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-50b3
  prompt: "Meanings: summon, propagate, transmit\nOnyomi: テン, デン\nKunyomi: つた.わる, つた.える, つた.う, つて"
  answers:
    - 傳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-50de
  prompt: "Meanings: lie, falsehood, deceive\nOnyomi: ギ, カ\nKunyomi: いつわ.る, いつわ.り, にせ"
  answers:
    - 僞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-50f9
  prompt: "Meanings: price, value\nOnyomi: カ, ケ\nKunyomi: あたい"
  answers:
    - 價
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5109
  prompt: "Meanings: economy, thrifty\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: つま.しい, つづまやか"
  answers:
    - 儉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5152
  prompt: "Meanings: child, young of animals\nOnyomi: ジ, ニ, ゲイ\nKunyomi: こ"
  answers:
    - 兒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-51a8
  prompt: "Meanings: enrich, wealthy, abundant\nOnyomi: フ, フウ\nKunyomi: と.む, とみ"
  answers:
    - 冨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-51c9
  prompt: "Meanings: nice and cool\nOnyomi: リョウ\nKunyomi: すず.しい, すず.む, すず.やか, うす.い"
  answers:
    - 凉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5269
  prompt: "Meanings: leftovers, residue, remains\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: あまつさえ, あま.り, あま.る"
  answers:
    - 剩
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-528d
  prompt: "Meanings: sword\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: つるぎ"
  answers:
    - 劍
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-52f3
  prompt: "Meanings: meritorious deed, merits, rank\nOnyomi: クン\nKunyomi: いさお"
  answers:
    - 勳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5377
  prompt: "Meanings: volume, book, part\nOnyomi: カン, ケン\nKunyomi: ま.く, まき"
  answers:
    - 卷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-537d
  prompt: "Meanings: promptly, namely\nOnyomi: ソク, ショク\nKunyomi: つ.く, すなわ.ち, もし"
  answers:
    - 卽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-55ae
  prompt: "Meanings: one, single, simple\nOnyomi: タン\nKunyomi: ひとえ"
  answers:
    - 單
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-56b4
  prompt: "Meanings: strictness, severity, rigidity\nOnyomi: ゲン, ゴン\nKunyomi: おごそ.か, きび.しい, いか.めしい, いつくし"
  answers:
    - 嚴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5708
  prompt: "Meanings: sphere, circle, radius\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: かこ.い"
  answers:
    - 圈
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-570b
  prompt: "Meanings: country\nOnyomi: コク\nKunyomi: くに"
  answers:
    - 國
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5713
  prompt: "Meanings: yen, circle, round\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: まる.い, まる, まど, まど.か"
  answers:
    - 圓
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5718
  prompt: "Meanings: association\nOnyomi: ダン, トン\nKunyomi: かたまり, まる.い"
  answers:
    - 團
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-57dc
  prompt: "Meanings: open country, field, wilderness\nOnyomi: ヤ, ショ\nKunyomi: の"
  answers:
    - 埜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-589e
  prompt: "Meanings: increase, add to, augment\nOnyomi: ゾウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: ます, ふえる, ふやす"
  answers:
    - 增
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-58d8
  prompt: "Meanings: fort, rampart, walls\nOnyomi: ルイ, ライ, スイ\nKunyomi: とりで"
  answers:
    - 壘
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-58de
  prompt: "Meanings: demolition, break, destroy\nOnyomi: カイ, エ\nKunyomi: こわ.す, こわ.れる, やぶ.る"
  answers:
    - 壞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-58ef
  prompt: "Meanings: big, large, robust\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: さかん"
  answers:
    - 壯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-58fd
  prompt: "Meanings: longevity, congratulations\nOnyomi: ジュ, ス, シュウ\nKunyomi: ことぶき, ことぶ.く, ことほ.ぐ"
  answers:
    - 壽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5967
  prompt: "Meanings: heart, interior\nOnyomi: オウ, オク\nKunyomi: おく.まる, くま"
  answers:
    - 奧
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-596c
  prompt: "Meanings: prize, reward, give award to\nOnyomi: ショウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: すす.める"
  answers:
    - 奬
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5b43
  prompt: "Meanings: girl, Miss, daughter\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: むすめ"
  answers:
    - 孃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5be6
  prompt: "Meanings: truth, reality\nOnyomi: ジツ, シツ\nKunyomi: み, みの.る, まこと.に, みの.り"
  answers:
    - 實
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5be2
  prompt: "Meanings: sleep, rest, bed chamber\nOnyomi: シン\nKunyomi: ね.る, ね.かす, い.ぬ, みたまや"
  answers:
    - 寢
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5bec
  prompt: "Meanings: broad, wide, spacious\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: ひろい, ゆるやか, くつろぐ"
  answers:
    - 寬
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5c07
  prompt: "Meanings: commander, general, admiral\nOnyomi: ショウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: まさ.に, はた, ひきい.る, もって"
  answers:
    - 將
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5c08
  prompt: "Meanings: specialty, exclusive, mainly\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: もっぱ.ら"
  answers:
    - 專
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5cef
  prompt: "Meanings: peak, summit\nOnyomi: ホウ\nKunyomi: みね, ね"
  answers:
    - 峯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5cfd
  prompt: "Meanings: gorge, strait, ravine\nOnyomi: キョウ, コウ\nKunyomi: はざま"
  answers:
    - 峽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5d8b
  prompt: "Meanings: island\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: しま"
  answers:
    - 嶋
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5de2
  prompt: "Meanings: nest, living quarter in tree\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: す, す.くう"
  answers:
    - 巢
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5e36
  prompt: "Meanings: belt, girdle, band\nOnyomi: タイ\nKunyomi: お.びる, おび"
  answers:
    - 帶
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5ee3
  prompt: "Meanings: broad, wide, spacious\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: ひろ.い, ひろ.まる, ひろ.める, ひろ.がる"
  answers:
    - 廣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5ef3
  prompt: "Meanings: hall, central room\nOnyomi: チョウ, テイ\nKunyomi: やくしょ"
  answers:
    - 廳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5f48
  prompt: "Meanings: bullet, twang, flip\nOnyomi: ダン, タン\nKunyomi: ひ.く, はず.む, たま, はじ.く"
  answers:
    - 彈
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5f4c
  prompt: "Meanings: extensive, full, fill\nOnyomi: ミ, ビ\nKunyomi: いや, や, あまねし, いよいよ"
  answers:
    - 彌
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5f9e
  prompt: "Meanings: from, by, since\nOnyomi: ジュウ, ショウ, ジュ\nKunyomi: したが.う, したが.える, より"
  answers:
    - 從
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5fb5
  prompt: "Meanings: summon, recruit, musical note\nOnyomi: チョウ, チ\nKunyomi: しるし, めす"
  answers:
    - 徵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-5fb7
  prompt: "Meanings: ethics, morality, virtue\nOnyomi: トク\nKunyomi: おしえ"
  answers:
    - 德
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6046
  prompt: "Meanings: constant, regular, persistent\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: つね.に"
  answers:
    - 恆
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-613c
  prompt: "Meanings: care, chastity\nOnyomi: シン\nKunyomi: つつし.む, つつし.み"
  answers:
    - 愼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-61f7
  prompt: "Meanings: pocket, feelings, heart\nOnyomi: カイ, エ\nKunyomi: ふところ, なつ.かしい, なつ.かしむ, なつ.く"
  answers:
    - 懷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-60e1
  prompt: "Meanings: bad, evil\nOnyomi: アク, オ\nKunyomi: わる.い, あ.し, にく.い, ああ"
  answers:
    - 惡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-60e0
  prompt: "Meanings: blessing, grace, favor\nOnyomi: ケイ, エ\nKunyomi: めぐ.む, めぐ.み"
  answers:
    - 惠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-61c9
  prompt: "Meanings: answer, yes, OK\nOnyomi: オウ, ヨウ\nKunyomi: あた.る, まさに, こた.える"
  answers:
    - 應
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6230
  prompt: "Meanings: war, fighting, battle\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: いくさ, たたか.う, おのの.く, そよぐ"
  answers:
    - 戰
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6232
  prompt: "Meanings: play, frolic, sport\nOnyomi: ギ, ゲ\nKunyomi: たわむ.れる, たわむ.れ"
  answers:
    - 戲
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-62d4
  prompt: "Meanings: extract, pull out, pilfer\nOnyomi: バツ, ハイ\nKunyomi: ぬ.く, ぬ.ける, ぬ.かす, ぬ.かる"
  answers:
    - 拔
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-62c2
  prompt: "Meanings: clear out, sweep away\nOnyomi: ヒツ, フツ, ホツ\nKunyomi: はら.う"
  answers:
    - 拂
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-641c
  prompt: "Meanings: search, seek, investigate\nOnyomi: ソウ, シュ, シュウ\nKunyomi: さが.す"
  answers:
    - 搜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-63ed
  prompt: "Meanings: raise, lift up, surname\nOnyomi: ケイ, ケツ\nKunyomi: かかげる"
  answers:
    - 揭
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6416
  prompt: "Meanings: wag, swing, wave\nOnyomi: ヨウ\nKunyomi: ゆ.れる, ゆ.らぐ, ゆ.るぐ, ゆ.する"
  answers:
    - 搖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-651d
  prompt: "Meanings: surrogate, act in addition to\nOnyomi: セツ, ショウ\nKunyomi: おさ.める, かね.る, と.る"
  answers:
    - 攝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-62dc
  prompt: "Meanings: worship, adore, pray to\nOnyomi: ハイ\nKunyomi: おが.む, おろが.む"
  answers:
    - 拜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-64ca
  prompt: "Meanings: strike, hit, beat\nOnyomi: ゲキ\nKunyomi: う.つ"
  answers:
    - 擊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-654d
  prompt: "Meanings: express, state, relate\nOnyomi: ジョ\nKunyomi: つい.ず, ついで"
  answers:
    - 敍
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6536
  prompt: "Meanings: income\nOnyomi: シュウ\nKunyomi: おさ.める, おさ.まる"
  answers:
    - 收
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-665d
  prompt: "Meanings: daytime, daylight\nOnyomi: チュウ\nKunyomi: ひる"
  answers:
    - 晝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-665a
  prompt: "Meanings: night, evening, late\nOnyomi: バン\nKunyomi: くれ, おそい"
  answers:
    - 晚
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-66c9
  prompt: "Meanings: dawn, daybreak, clear\nOnyomi: キョウ, ギョウ\nKunyomi: あかつき, さと.る"
  answers:
    - 曉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-66c6
  prompt: "Meanings: calendar, era\nOnyomi: レキ, リャク\nKunyomi: こよみ"
  answers:
    - 曆
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-66fe
  prompt: "Meanings: once, before, formerly\nOnyomi: ソウ, ソ, ゾウ\nKunyomi: かつ.て, か.って, すなわち"
  answers:
    - 曾
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-689d
  prompt: "Meanings: article, counter for articles, clauses, paragraphs, etc., twig\nOnyomi: ジョウ, チョウ, デキ\nKunyomi: えだ, すじ"
  answers:
    - 條
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-69ae
  prompt: "Meanings: flourish, prosperity, honour\nOnyomi: エイ, ヨウ\nKunyomi: さか.える, は.える, え"
  answers:
    - 榮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6a02
  prompt: "Meanings: music, comfort\nOnyomi: ガク, ラク, ゴウ\nKunyomi: たの.しい, たの.しむ, この.む"
  answers:
    - 樂
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6a23
  prompt: "Meanings: Esq., way, manner\nOnyomi: ヨウ, ショウ\nKunyomi: さま"
  answers:
    - 樣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6a6b
  prompt: "Meanings: across, horizontal, lateral\nOnyomi: オウ, コウ\nKunyomi: よこ, よこたわる, よこたえる"
  answers:
    - 橫
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6aa2
  prompt: "Meanings: check, examine\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: しら.べる"
  answers:
    - 檢
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6afb
  prompt: "Meanings: cherry\nOnyomi: オウ, ヨウ\nKunyomi: さくら"
  answers:
    - 櫻
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-76dc
  prompt: "Meanings: thief, to steal\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: ぬす.む"
  answers:
    - 盜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6b65
  prompt: "Meanings: step, pace, walk\nOnyomi: ホ, ブ, フ\nKunyomi: あるく, あゆむ, あゆみ"
  answers:
    - 步
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6b77
  prompt: "Meanings: take place, past, history"
  answers:
    - 歷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6bcf
  prompt: "Meanings: every, each\nOnyomi: マイ, バイ\nKunyomi: つね"
  answers:
    - 每
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6c23
  prompt: "Meanings: spirit, mind, air\nOnyomi: キ, ケ\nKunyomi: いき"
  answers:
    - 氣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6d89
  prompt: "Meanings: ford stream, wade across\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: わたる, かかわる"
  answers:
    - 涉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6de8
  prompt: "Meanings: pure, clean, unspoiled\nOnyomi: ジョウ, セイ\nKunyomi: きよ.める, きよ.い"
  answers:
    - 淨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6dda
  prompt: "Meanings: tears, weep, cry\nOnyomi: ルイ, レイ\nKunyomi: なみだ"
  answers:
    - 淚
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6e34
  prompt: "Meanings: thirsty, parched, yearn\nOnyomi: カツ\nKunyomi: かわ.く, かわき"
  answers:
    - 渴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6eab
  prompt: "Meanings: lukewarm, warm, tepid\nOnyomi: オン, ウン\nKunyomi: あたたか, あたためる"
  answers:
    - 溫
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6eef
  prompt: "Meanings: block up, obstruct, stagnant\nOnyomi: タイ, テイ\nKunyomi: とどこお.る"
  answers:
    - 滯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6f81
  prompt: "Meanings: astringent, harsh, uneven\nOnyomi: ジュウ, シュウ\nKunyomi: しぶ, しぶ.い, しぶ.る"
  answers:
    - 澁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-6fd5
  prompt: "Meanings: wet, moist, humid\nOnyomi: シツ, シュウ\nKunyomi: しめ.る, しめ.す, うるお.う, うるお.す"
  answers:
    - 濕
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7027
  prompt: "Meanings: waterfall, rapids, cascade\nOnyomi: ロウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: たき"
  answers:
    - 瀧
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7028
  prompt: "Meanings: swift current, rapids\nOnyomi: ライ\nKunyomi: せ"
  answers:
    - 瀨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-71c8
  prompt: "Meanings: lamp, light, counter for lights\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: ひ, ほ-, ともしび, とも.す"
  answers:
    - 燈
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-71d2
  prompt: "Meanings: burn, bake, heat\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: や.く, や.ける"
  answers:
    - 燒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-722d
  prompt: "Meanings: to dispute, fight, contend\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: あらそ.う, いか.でか"
  answers:
    - 爭
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7232
  prompt: "Meanings: change, be of use, reach to\nOnyomi: イ\nKunyomi: ため, な.る, な.す, す.る"
  answers:
    - 爲
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-72f9
  prompt: "Meanings: narrow, contract, reduce\nOnyomi: キョウ, コウ\nKunyomi: せま.い, せば.める, せば.まる, さ"
  answers:
    - 狹
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-72c0
  prompt: "Meanings: form, appearance, shape\nOnyomi: ジョウ"
  answers:
    - 狀
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9ed8
  prompt: "Meanings: silent, quiet, still\nOnyomi: ボク, モク\nKunyomi: だ.まる, もだ.す"
  answers:
    - 默
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7378
  prompt: "Meanings: beast, animal, bestial\nOnyomi: ジュウ\nKunyomi: けもの, けだもの"
  answers:
    - 獸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-758a
  prompt: "Meanings: tatami, counter for tatami mats, fold\nOnyomi: ジョウ, チョウ\nKunyomi: たた.む, たたみ, かさ.なる, かさ.ねる"
  answers:
    - 疊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7626
  prompt: "Meanings: thin, emaciated, lean\nOnyomi: ソウ, チュウ, シュウ, チュ\nKunyomi: やせ.る"
  answers:
    - 瘦
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-76c3
  prompt: "Meanings: glass, cup\nOnyomi: ハイ\nKunyomi: さかずき"
  answers:
    - 盃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-76e1
  prompt: "Meanings: exhaust, use up, run out of\nOnyomi: ジン, サン\nKunyomi: つ.くす, つ.きる, つ.かす, さかづき"
  answers:
    - 盡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-771e
  prompt: "Meanings: truth, reality, Buddhist sect\nOnyomi: シン\nKunyomi: ま, まこと"
  answers:
    - 眞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-788e
  prompt: "Meanings: break, smash, broken\nOnyomi: サイ\nKunyomi: くだ.く, くだ.ける"
  answers:
    - 碎
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7955
  prompt: "Meanings: mysterious, secret, abstruse\nOnyomi: ヒ\nKunyomi: ひ.める, かく.す"
  answers:
    - 祕
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-79aa
  prompt: "Meanings: Zen Buddhism, silent meditation\nOnyomi: ゼン, セン\nKunyomi: しずか, ゆず.る"
  answers:
    - 禪
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-79ae
  prompt: "Meanings: social custom, manners, courtesy\nOnyomi: レイ, ライ"
  answers:
    - 禮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7a3b
  prompt: "Meanings: rice plant\nOnyomi: トウ, テ\nKunyomi: いね, いな-"
  answers:
    - 稻
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7a57
  prompt: "Meanings: ear (of grain), head, crest (of wave)\nOnyomi: スイ\nKunyomi: ほ"
  answers:
    - 穗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7cb9
  prompt: "Meanings: pure, unadulterated, select\nOnyomi: スイ\nKunyomi: いき"
  answers:
    - 粹
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7da0
  prompt: "Meanings: green, chlorine\nOnyomi: リョク, ロク\nKunyomi: みどり"
  answers:
    - 綠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7dd6
  prompt: "Meanings: end of thread, thread, clue\nOnyomi: ショ, チョ\nKunyomi: お, いとぐち"
  answers:
    - 緖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7de3
  prompt: "Meanings: hem, margin, reason\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: ふち, へり, よる"
  answers:
    - 緣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7e23
  prompt: "Meanings: county, district, subdivision\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: か.ける"
  answers:
    - 縣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7e31
  prompt: "Meanings: indulge in, give free reign to\nOnyomi: ジュウ\nKunyomi: たて"
  answers:
    - 縱
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-7e96
  prompt: "Meanings: fine, slender, thin kimono\nOnyomi: セン"
  answers:
    - 纖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-807d
  prompt: "Meanings: careful enquiry, headstrong\nOnyomi: チョウ\nKunyomi: き.く, ゆる.す"
  answers:
    - 聽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-81df
  prompt: "Meanings: viscera, bowels\nOnyomi: ゾウ\nKunyomi: はらわた"
  answers:
    - 臟
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8207
  prompt: "Meanings: participate in, give, award\nOnyomi: ヨ\nKunyomi: あた.える, あずか.る, くみ.する, ともに"
  answers:
    - 與
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-838a
  prompt: "Meanings: broom\nOnyomi: ソウ, ショウ, チャン\nKunyomi: ほうき, おごそ.か"
  answers:
    - 莊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-842c
  prompt: "Meanings: ten thousand, 10,000\nOnyomi: マン, バン\nKunyomi: よろず"
  answers:
    - 萬
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8597
  prompt: "Meanings: garden, yard, farm\nOnyomi: エン, オン\nKunyomi: その"
  answers:
    - 薗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-85cf
  prompt: "Meanings: hide, own, have\nOnyomi: ゾウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: くら, おさ.める, かく.れる"
  answers:
    - 藏
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-85b0
  prompt: "Meanings: a medicinal herb, to cauterize\nOnyomi: クン\nKunyomi: かおる, かおりぐさ, かおり"
  answers:
    - 薰
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-85dd
  prompt: "Meanings: art, craft, performance\nOnyomi: ゲイ, ウン\nKunyomi: う.える, のり, わざ"
  answers:
    - 藝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-85e5
  prompt: "Meanings: medicine, chemical, enamel\nOnyomi: ヤク\nKunyomi: くすり"
  answers:
    - 藥
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-865b
  prompt: "Meanings: false, worthless, empty\nOnyomi: キョ, コ\nKunyomi: むなしい"
  answers:
    - 虛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-885e
  prompt: "Meanings: defense\nOnyomi: エイ, エ\nKunyomi: まも.る"
  answers:
    - 衞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-88dd
  prompt: "Meanings: dress, pretend, disguise\nOnyomi: ソウ, ショウ\nKunyomi: よそお.う, よそお.い"
  answers:
    - 裝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-89bd
  prompt: "Meanings: look at, inspect, perceive\nOnyomi: ラン\nKunyomi: み.る"
  answers:
    - 覽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8b20
  prompt: "Meanings: chant (esp. Noh), folksong, ballad\nOnyomi: ヨウ\nKunyomi: うた.う, うた"
  answers:
    - 謠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8b93
  prompt: "Meanings: allow, permit, yield\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: ゆず.る"
  answers:
    - 讓
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8ce3
  prompt: "Meanings: sell, betray, show off\nOnyomi: バイ\nKunyomi: う.る, う.れる"
  answers:
    - 賣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8cf4
  prompt: "Meanings: rely, depend on, accuse falsely\nOnyomi: ライ\nKunyomi: たのむ, たよる, たより"
  answers:
    - 賴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-8f49
  prompt: "Meanings: shift, move, turn\nOnyomi: テン\nKunyomi: ころ.がる, ころ.げる, ころ.がす, ころ.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 轉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-90de
  prompt: "Meanings: gentleman\nOnyomi: ロウ\nKunyomi: おとこ"
  answers:
    - 郞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9189
  prompt: "Meanings: get drunk, feel sick, poisoned\nOnyomi: スイ\nKunyomi: よ.う, よ.い"
  answers:
    - 醉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-91c0
  prompt: "Meanings: brew, cause\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: かも.す"
  answers:
    - 釀
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9304
  prompt: "Meanings: copy, write down, record\nOnyomi: ロク, リョ\nKunyomi: しるす"
  answers:
    - 錄
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-934a
  prompt: "Meanings: smelt metals, forge, refine\nOnyomi: レン\nKunyomi: ねる"
  answers:
    - 鍊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-93ad
  prompt: "Meanings: ancient peace-preservation centers\nOnyomi: チン\nKunyomi: しず.める, しず.まる, おさえ"
  answers:
    - 鎭
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9444
  prompt: "Meanings: cast, mint\nOnyomi: チュウ, シュ, シュウ\nKunyomi: い.る"
  answers:
    - 鑄
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9677
  prompt: "Meanings: fall into, cave in, fall (castle)\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: おちい.る, おとしい.れる"
  answers:
    - 陷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-96aa
  prompt: "Meanings: inaccessible place, impregnable position, steep place\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: けわ.しい"
  answers:
    - 險
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-96dc
  prompt: "Meanings: mixed, blended, mix\nOnyomi: ザツ, ゾウ\nKunyomi: まじ.える, まじ.る"
  answers:
    - 雜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-975c
  prompt: "Meanings: quiet\nOnyomi: セイ, ジョウ\nKunyomi: しず-, しず.か, しず.まる, しず.める"
  answers:
    - 靜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-986f
  prompt: "Meanings: manifest, display, evident\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: あきらか, あらわ.れる"
  answers:
    - 顯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-98dc
  prompt: "Meanings: flip over, upset, capsize\nOnyomi: ハン, ホン\nKunyomi: ひるがえ.す, ひるがえ.る"
  answers:
    - 飜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-99c8
  prompt: "Meanings: run, gallop, advance\nOnyomi: ク\nKunyomi: か.ける, か.る"
  answers:
    - 駈
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9a37
  prompt: "Meanings: harass, bother, annoy\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: さわ.ぐ, うれい, さわが.しい"
  answers:
    - 騷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9a57
  prompt: "Meanings: verification, effect, testing\nOnyomi: ケン, ゲン\nKunyomi: あかし, しるし, ため.す, ためし"
  answers:
    - 驗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9aee
  prompt: "Meanings: hair\nOnyomi: ハツ\nKunyomi: かみ"
  answers:
    - 髮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9dc4
  prompt: "Meanings: chicken\nOnyomi: ケイ\nKunyomi: にわとり, とり"
  answers:
    - 鷄
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9ec3
  prompt: "Meanings: yellow, surname\nOnyomi: コウ, オウ\nKunyomi: き"
  answers:
    - 黃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9ed1
  prompt: "Meanings: black, dark, evil\nOnyomi: コク\nKunyomi: くろい, くろ"
  answers:
    - 黑
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9f4a
  prompt: "Meanings: alike, equal, similar\nOnyomi: セイ, サイ\nKunyomi: そろ.う, ひと.しい, ひと.しく, あたる"
  answers:
    - 齊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-jinmeiyo-9f8d
  prompt: "Meanings: dragon, imperial\nOnyomi: リュウ, リョウ, ロウ\nKunyomi: たつ"
  answers:
    - 龍
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
